Philip M. Wagner papers
1839-1995
- Series I. Personal, 1839-1994; bulk 1950-1983; 6 boxes (7.5 linear feet)
  - Sub-series I.D. Research Files, 49 folders (1.25 linear feet)
    - Hanford Miniature Swine (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Harper, Ralph (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Hill, Joh Philip (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - India (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - Maps (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - Maryland Guide Book (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - Mencken, H.L. 1950’s (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Mencken, H.L. 1960’s (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - Mencken, H.L. 1980-1988 (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - Mencken, H.L. 1989 (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - Mencken, H.L. 1990’s (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - Mencken, H.L. miscellaneous (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - National Conference of Editorial Writers (Box 4, Folder 43)
    - Nixon, Richard (Box 4, Folder 44)
    - Press (Box 4, Folder 45)
    - Press Conference Article (Box 4, Folder 46)
    - Reagan,Ronald (Box 4, Folder 47)
    - Trips - Canada 1972 (Box 4, Folder 48)
    - University of California Publications (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Sub-series I.E. Publications, 1929-1967; bulk 1953-1967; 7 folders (.25 linear feet)
    Miscellaneous publications by Philip M. Wagner arranged in chronological order by publication date.
    - Misc. pubs: 1929 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Misc. pubs: 1946-1949 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Misc. pubs: 1953 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Misc. pubs: 1958 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Misc. pubs: 1961 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Misc. pubs: 1963 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Misc. pubs: 1967 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Sub-series I.F. Journals and Pamphlets, 1896-1922; bulk 1951-1980; 24 folders (.5 linear feet)
    Miscellaneous journals and pamphlets collected by Wagner.
    - 1896 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - 1932 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - 1943 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - 1950 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - 1951 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - 1952 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - 1953 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - 1953 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - 1954 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - 1955 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - 1957 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - 1959 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - 1960 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - 1961 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - 1962 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - 1963 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - 1967 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - 1971 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - 1972 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - 1977 (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - 1979 (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - 1982 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - 1986 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - 1988 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - 1992 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Sub-series I.G. Receipts and Invoices, 1951-1973; 5 folders (.25 linear feet)
    Receipts, invoices, statements and vouchers many pertaining to Wagners European trips arranged in chronological order.
    - 1951 (European Trip) (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - 1956 (European Trip) (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - 1960 (European Trip) (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - 1971 (misc.) (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - 1972 (misc.) (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - 1973 (misc.) (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Sub-series I.H. Diaries, 1960-1962, 1970; 1 folder (.25 linear feet)
    Handwritten diary pages; incomplete. Arranged in date order.
    - May 1960 - July 1961, July 1962, & Feb. 1070 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Sub-series I.I. Photos, undated; 1 folder (.25 linear feet)
    Photos of Philip Wagner, the sun staff and other individuals; many identified.
    - Misc. many identified on back (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Sub-series I.J. Flyers, Announcements and Miscellany, 1934-1984; 2 folders (.25 linear feet)
    Miscellaneous handbills and announcements and a proclamation.
    - Miscellaneous Flyers & Awards (Box 5, Folder 41)
    - Proclamation; San Antonio TX. 1940 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Sub-series I.K. Notes and Notebooks, 1987-1997, undated; bulk 1983-1997; 3 folders (.25 linear feet)
    Miscellaneous handwritten notes, a notebook with inscription ‘Eddie Wagner’, and a collection of biographical and autobiographical materials on Philip Wagner containing manuscript drafts, notes, clippings, and obituaries.
    - Notes 1929, 1962, and undated (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - Notebook inscribed Eddie Wagner (Box 5, Folder 44)
    - Miscellaneous Biographical notes, clippings and obituaries (Box 5, Folder 45)
    - 4 Books of Photos, 1 Book of Clippings, 1 Set of promotional material on Columbia MD. 1960 (Box 6)